Guide to the Yale University Library Name/Title Card Catalog
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- University of Hong Kong (Box 8191)
- University of Illinois. College of education (Box 8192)
- University of Iowa. Studies (Box 8193)
- University of Kansas. M. (Box 8194)
- University of Liverpool (Box 8195)
- University of London. London school of... (Box 8196)
- University of Manchester. Publication (Box 8197)
- University of Michigan (author) (Box 8198)
- University of Michigan. Joint... (Box 8199)
- University of Minnesota. Studies (Box 8200)
- University of Missouri (Box 8201)
- University of Nebraska. D. (Box 8202)
- University of North Carolina (Box 8203)
- University of Notre Dame (Box 8204)
- University of Ottawa (Box 8205)
- University of Oxford (author) (O) (Box 8206)
- University of Oxford. Hertford College (Box 8207)
- University of Oxford (subject) (N) (Box 8208)
- University of Oxford-History (Box 8209)
- University of Pennsylvania. Department of m. (Box 8210)
- University of Pittsburgh Press (Box 8211)
- University of Rochester (Box 8212)
- University of South Africa (Box 8213)
- University of Stellenbosch (Box 8214)
- University of Texas. Chemical (Box 8215)
- University of the O. (Box 8216)
- University of the State of New York. Proceedings (Box 8217)
- University of Toronto. History and economics (Box 8218)
- University of Virginia. R. (Box 8219)
- University of Washington. China (Box 8220)
- University of Wisconsin. Studies in Language and Literature (Box 8221)
- University of Zambia. Institute for S. (Box 8222)
- Univerzitet u Beogradu (Box 8223)
- Uniwersytet Warszawski (Box 8224)
- Uno, Tofu (Box 8225)
- Unspeakable s. (Box 8226)
- Untersee, P. (Box 8227)
- Unterwalden (Box 8228)
- Up from E. (Box 8229)
- Updike, J. (Box 8230)
- Upper v. (Box 8231)
- Upravlenie G. (Box 8232)
- Uralier und I. (Box 8233)
- Urban and rural (Box 8234)
- Urban Institute paper (Box 8235)
- Urbanek, V. (Box 8236)
- Urdanoz, T. (Box 8237)
- Uriconium (Box 8238)
- Urquidi, C. (Box 8239)
- Uruguay (author) (Box 8240)
- Urvaci (Box 8241)
- Used book (Box 8242)
- Usi (Box 8243)
- Ussher (Box 8244)
- Usual politics (Box 8245)
- Utah in (Box 8246)
- Utilization of (Box 8247)
- Utsumi, S. (Box 8248)
- Uy, A. (Box 8249)
- V (Box 8250)
- V.M. (Box 8251)
- Vacano, O. (Box 8252)
- Vadeev, O. (Box 8253)
- Vagner, L. (Box 8254)
- Vain (Box 8255)
- Vajk, J. (Box 8256)
- Valcarcel, D. (Box 8257)
- Valdivieso, J. (Box 8258)
- Valenti, A. (Box 8259)
- Valenzuela, H. (Box 8260)
- Valery, Paul (subject) (Box 8261)
- Valk, M. (Box 8262)
- Valle (Box 8263)
- Vallejo, D. (Box 8264)
- Vallmark, P. (Box 8265)
- Valqui, C. (Box 8266)
- Vampire bat (Box 8267)
- Van Biema, C. (Box 8268)
- Vancouver (Box 8269)
- Van Denburg (Box 8270)
- Van der Kiste, J. (Box 8271)
- Vander Wal, C. (Box 8272)
- Van Dorn (Box 8273)
- Vanech, W. (Box 8274)
- Van Heusen (Box 8275)
- Van Laar (Box 8276)
- Van Nostrand (Box 8277)
- Van Santvoord (Box 8278)
- Van Vactor, L. (Box 8279)
- Van Zeeland, P. (Box 8280)
- Varela (Box 8281)
- Vargas, L. (Box 8282)
- Varietes sinologiques (Box 8283)
- Varma, V. (Box 8284)
- Varsik, Branislav (Box 8285)
- Vasconcelos, J. (Box 8286)
- Vasil'ev, V.G. (Box 8287)
- Vass (Box 8288)
- Vatai, L. (Box 8289)
- Vattasso, M. (Box 8290)
- Vaughan, J. (Box 8291)
- Vaux, R. (Box 8292)
- Vazquez de Espinosa (Box 8293)
- Vechner, D. (Box 8294)
- Vedder, Henry Clay (Box 8295)
- Vega, G. (Box 8296)
- Vegas, A. (Box 8297)
- Veinte cuentos p. (Box 8298)
- Velasco (Box 8299)
- Velde, W. (Box 8300)
- Velikii (Box 8301)
- Velpeau (Box 8302)
- Vendo (Box 8303)
- Venezuela. Comision E. (Box 8304)
- Venezuela. Ministerio de Minas (Box 8305)
- Venice. Comitato Centrale (Box 8306)
- Vennard (Box 8307)
- Venturi (Box 8308)
- Veraghtert (Box 8309)
- Verbik (Box 8310)
- Verdam (Box 8311)
- Verein (Box 8312)
- Verein fur Socialpolitik. Schriften... no. 103 (Box 8313)
- Vereniging (Box 8314)
- Verga, Giovanni, 1840-1922-Bibliography (Box 8315)
- Vergnani (Box 8316)
- Verhein (Box 8317)
- Verkhy (Box 8318)
- Vermeer, Hendrina (Box 8319)
- Vermont. Laws, statutes, etc. (Box 8320)
- Vernam (Box 8321)
- Vernon, F. (Box 8322)
- Veroeffentlichungen aus dem U. (Box 8323)
- Veroeffentlichungen der Kommission fuer Zeitgeschichte bei... (Box 8324)
- Veroeffentlichungen des Staatsarchivs (Box 8325)
- Verrill, Alpheus (Box 8326)
- Version (Box 8327)
- Versus (Box 8328)
- Verwey, E. (Box 8329)
- Veselitskaia (Box 8330)
- Veste (Box 8331)
- Vetter (Box 8332)
- Via della (Box 8333)
- Vialon (Box 8334)
- Viazemskii (Box 8335)
- Vichitvong (Box 8336)
- Victor (surname) (Box 8337)
- Victoria (titles, etc.) (Box 8338)
- Victoria history of the county of Devon (Box 8339)
- Victorians (Box 8340)
- Vida ignorada (Box 8341)
- Vidas e. (Box 8342)
- Vie dans (Box 8343)
- Viedina (Box 8344)
- Vienna (author) (Box 8345)
- Viennese h. (Box 8346)
- Viertler (Box 8347)
- Vietnam. V. (Box 8348)
- View (Box 8349)
- Vigezzi (Box 8350)
- Vigny, Alfred Victor, comte de, 1797-1863. Brach (Box 8351)
- Viktoria. (Box 8352)
- Vilhelm Anderson (Box 8353)
- Villaespesa (Box 8354)
- Villani (Box 8355)
- Villas, J. (Box 8356)
- Villemain (Box 8357)
- Villiers du Terrage (Box 8358)
- Vimercati (Box 8359)
- Vincent, J (Box 8360)
- Vindication (Box 8361)
- Viney (Box 8362)
- Vinogradov, Vladilen (Box 8363)
- Violence m. (Box 8364)
- Virchow (Box 8365)
- Virgil (Individual works) (translations) Aeneis (subject) (Box 8366)
- Virgil-Concordances (Box 8367)
- Virginia. General Assembly (Box 8368)
- Virginia Historical Society (Box 8369)
- Virmond (Box 8370)
- Vischer, R. (Box 8371)
- Vision and f. (Box 8372)
- Visits (Box 8373)
- Visualized (Box 8374)
- Vital c. (Box 8375)
- Vito (Box 8376)
- Vitu (Box 8377)
- Vivian (Box 8378)
- Vizetelly, H. (Box 8379)
- Vlahovic, V. (Box 8380)
- Vnartig (Box 8381)
- Vocational (Box 8382)
- Voelcker (Box 8383)
- Voet, L. (Box 8384)
- Vogel, Z. (Box 8385)
- Vogt, P. (Box 8386)
- Voices o. (Box 8387)
- Voirin (Box 8388)
- Volcanological (Box 8389)
- Volkheimer (Box 8390)
- Volkslieder (Box 8391)
- Vollmer (Box 8392)
- Voza (Box 8393)
- Voltaire, Francois Marie Arouet de, 1694-1778 (Individual works) Defense de mon (Box 8394)
- Voltaire, Francois M.A. de (subject) (Box 8395)
- Volunteer (Box 8396)
- Vom Z. (Box 8397)
- Von Berndt (Box 8398)
- Von Gizycki (Box 8399)
- Von Molnar (Box 8400)
- Von Z. (Box 8401)
- Voprosy khudozhestvennogo t. (Box 8402)
- Vordtriede (Box 8403)
- Voronova (Box 8404)
- Vos der (Box 8405)
- Voss, K. (Box 8406)
- Vou (Box 8407)
- Voyage of the V. (Box 8408)
- Vozniuk (Box 8409)
- Vrey (Box 8410)
- Vroven's (Box 8411)
- Vsesoiuznoe n. (Box 8412)
- Vstriecha. (Box 8413)
- Vukomanovic (Box 8414)
- Vvedenskii (Box 8415)
- Vysotskii (Box 8416)
- W., M. (Box 8417)
- W.P.S. (Box 8418)
- Wabash m. (Box 8419)
- Wackerbarth (Box 8420)
- Wade (Box 8421)
- Wadsworth, M. (Box 8422)
- Wafer (Box 8423)
- Wagenheim, O. (Box 8424)
- Wagner, Christoph (Box 8425)
- Wagner, L. (Box 8426)
- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883 (subject) (S) (Box 8427)
- Wahab A. (Box 8428)
- Wahrheit (Box 8429)
- Waine (Box 8430)
- Waiting for the u. (Box 8431)
- Wake, P. (Box 8432)
- Waksman, S. (Box 8433)
- Wald, K. (Box 8434)
- Waldman (Box 8435)
- Wales, Great Britain (author) (Box 8436)
- Walker (surname) (Box 8437)
- Walker, F. (Box 8438)
- Walker, John, 1770-1831 (Box 8439)
- Walker, Stuart (Box 8440)
- Walkley (Box 8441)
- Wallace, David R. (Box 8442)
- Wallace, S. (Box 8443)
- Wallenreiter (Box 8444)
- Wallin (Box 8445)
- Wallon (Box 8446)
- Walpole, Horace (author) Il Castello di Otranto. (Box 8447)
- Walpole, Robert, 1676-1745 (subject) (Box 8448)
- Walsh, J. (Box 8449)
- Walt Disney Productions (Box 8450)
- Walter, Rolf (Box 8451)
- Waltham (Box 8452)
- Walton, Izaak (author) (Box 8453)
- Waltz, R. (Box 8454)
- Wan K. (Box 8455)
- Wanderer and t. (Box 8456)
- Wang, Ch'ang-lu (Box 8457)
- Wang, Chien, fl. 1778 (Box 8458)
- Wang, Chung-min (Box 8459)
- Wang, Dscheng, 1900- (Box 8460)
- Wang hsiang k. (Box 8461)
- Wang, I-jen (Box 8462)
- Wang, Kuo-wei (Box 8463)
- Wang, Ming-shih (Box 8464)
- Wang, Shih-chen, 1634-1711 (Box 8465)
- Wang, Ta-i (Box 8466)
- Wang, Tzu-chieh (Box 8467)
- Wang, Yi-t'ung (Box 8468)
- Wangemann (Box 8469)
- Wapasha (Box 8470)
- War medicine (Box 8471)
- Warburg Institute (Box 8472)
- Ward, David (Box 8473)
- Ward, John (Box 8474)
- Ward, Seth (Box 8475)
- Warder (Box 8476)
- Warera n. (Box 8477)
- Warman (Box 8478)
- Warner, J. (Box 8479)
- Warning (Box 8480)
- Warren, H. (Box 8481)
- Warren, Sandra (Box 8482)
- Warsaw. Teatr (Box 8483)
- Warton (surname) (Box 8484)
- Wasatch (Box 8485)
- Washburne (Box 8486)
- Washington, George, 1732-1799 (subject) (L) (Box 8487)
- Washington (D.C.) (Box 8488)
- Washington (D.C.) Public library (Box 8489)
- Washington (State) State Game Commission (Box 8490)
- Washington Post (Box 8491)
- Wasi, M. (Box 8492)
- Wassermann, K. (Box 8493)
- Watakushi wa mo (Box 8494)
- Watch (Box 8495)
- Water Resources Engineers (Box 8496)
- Waterloo book (Box 8497)
- Watertown (Box 8498)
- Watney (Box 8499)
- Watson, H. (Box 8500)
- Watson, Robert (Box 8501)
- Watt, J. (Box 8502)
- Watts, E. (Box 8503)
- Watts, W. (Box 8504)
- Waveforms (Box 8505)
- Way to r. (Box 8506)
- Wayside Violet (Box 8507)
- Wealth and H. (Box 8508)
- Weaver, J. (Box 8509)
- Webb, H. (Box 8510)
- Webber (Box 8511)
- Weber, Ernst (Box 8512)
- Weber, Max (Box 8513)
- Weber, Wilhelm E. (Box 8514)
- Webster, Donald (Box 8515)
- Webster, Noah, 1758-1843 (author) International (Box 8516)
- Weck (Box 8517)
- Wedenberg, Erik (Box 8518)
- Weekly (Box 8519)
- Weems (Box 8520)
- Wege der G. (Box 8521)
- Wehde (Box 8522)
- Wei chi pao (Box 8523)
- Wei lu yeh (Box 8524)
- Wei wo (Box 8525)
- Weidenmueller (Box 8526)
- Weigert, B. (Box 8527)
- Weil, S. (Box 8528)
- Weimarer (Box 8529)
- Weiner, E. (Box 8530)
- Weinreich, O. (Box 8531)
- Weir, John (Box 8532)
- Weiser (Box 8533)
- Weiss, E. (Box 8534)
- Weiss, Peter (Box 8535)
- Weissert, O. (Box 8536)
- Weitzner, B. (Box 8537)
- Welch, Robert (Box 8538)
- Welfare economics (Box 8539)
- Weller (Box 8540)
- Wellhouse (Box 8541)
- Wellmann (Box 8542)
- Wells, C. (Box 8543)
- Wells, H.G. (author) Joan and Peter (Box 8544)
- Wells, P. (Box 8545)
- Welsh, J. (Box 8546)
- Welti, F. (Box 8547)
- Wen che sui (Box 8548)
- Wen hsueh pai (Box 8549)
- Wen i yen (Box 8550)
- Wen tzu (Box 8551)
- Wendland (Box 8552)
- Wenger, L. (Box 8553)
- Went, I. (Box 8554)
- Wer r. (Box 8555)
- Werken u. (Box 8556)
- Werner, J. (Box 8557)
- Werry (Box 8558)
- Weschke, H. (Box 8559)
- Wesley, John, 1703-1791 (subject) (Box 8560)
- Wessels (Box 8561)
- West, G. (Box 8562)
- West, S. (Box 8563)
- West Florida (Box 8564)
- West Roxbury, Mass. (Box 8565)
- Westall (Box 8566)
- Westerheide (Box 8567)
- Western Australia (author) (Box 8568)
- Western History (Box 8569)
- Western Reserve (titles, etc.) (Box 8570)
- Westervelt (Box 8571)
- Westmacott (Box 8572)
- Weston (Box 8573)
- Westropp (Box 8574)
- Westwood, Joseph (Box 8575)
- Wettstein, K. (Box 8576)
- Weyl (Box 8577)
- Whall (Box 8578)
- Wharton (titles, etc.) (Box 8579)
- What is local (Box 8580)
- Whatley (Box 8581)
- Whedon, John (Box 8582)
- Wheeler, R. (Box 8583)
- Wheildon (Box 8584)
- Where bonds (Box 8585)
- Which way (Box 8586)
- Whipple (titles, etc.) (Box 8587)
- Whiston, William (subject) (Box 8588)
- White (surname) (Box 8589)
- White, Charles, fl. 1843-1877 (Box 8590)
- White, George A. (Box 8591)
- White, John, 17th cent. (Box 8592)
- White, O. (Box 8593)
- White, Thomas A. (Box 8594)
- White Company (Box 8595)
- White rose (Box 8596)
- Whitehead (Box 8597)
- Whitehouse (Box 8598)
- Whitgrave (Box 8599)
- Whitman, C. (Box 8600)
- Whitman, Walt (subject) (Box 8601)
- Whitney, G. (Box 8602)
- Whitredge (Box 8603)
- Whittier, John Greenleaf (Individual works) (Box 8604)
- Whitworth A. (Box 8605)
- Whole h. (Box 8606)
- Who's who in the E. (Box 8607)
- Whyte (Box 8608)
- Wichert (Box 8609)
- Wickham, H. (Box 8610)
- Widener (Box 8611)
- Widyaparwa (Box 8612)
- Wiedenau (Box 8613)
- Wieland, Christoph Martin (subject) (Box 8614)
- Wiener, M. (Box 8615)
- Wiener Z. (Box 8616)
- Wiesenhoefer (Box 8617)
- Wigan (Box 8618)
- Wigmore (Box 8619)
- Wiksell (Box 8620)
- Wilbur, S. (Box 8621)
- Wild (Box 8622)
- Wilde (Box 8623)
- Wildebauer (Box 8624)
- Wilder, Thornton, 1897-1975. Heaven's (Box 8625)
- Wildlife m. (Box 8626)
- Wiley series o. (Box 8627)
- Wilhelm R. (Box 8628)
- Wilkes, John A. (Box 8629)
- Wilkinson, C. (Box 8630)
- Wilks, T. (Box 8631)
- Willard, John (Box 8632)
- Willems (Box 8633)
- William (Box 8634)
- William, of Saint-Thierry, Abbot of Saint-Thierry, ca. 1085-1148? (Box 8635)
- William G. (Box 8636)
- Williams, Alfred (Box 8637)
- Williams, Clark (Box 8638)
- Williams, F. (Box 8639)
- Williams, Henry (Box 8640)
- Williams, John, 1817-1899 (Box 8641)
- Williams, Matt (Box 8642)
- Williams, Roger, 1604?-1683 (author) (Box 8643)
- Williams, Tennessee, 1911-. The Two-Character play (Box 8644)
- Williams, William Carlos. Something to Say (Box 8645)
- Williamson, B. (Box 8646)
- Williamson, R.M. (Box 8647)
- Willis, G. (Box 8648)
- Williston (Box 8649)
- Willoughby, William F. (Box 8650)
- Wilman (Box 8651)
- Wilson, Aileen (Box 8652)
- Wilson, Daniel (Box 8653)
- Wilson, Erasmus (Box 8654)
- Wilson, Henry (Box 8655)
- Wilson, John, 1804-1875 (Box 8656)
- Wilson, Michele (Box 8657)
- Wilson, Roy Arthur (Box 8658)
- Wilson, Woodrow, 1856-1924 (author) (L) (Box 8659)
- Wily (Box 8660)
- Winchester (surname) (Box 8661)
- Wind (titles, phrases, etc.) (Box 8662)
- Windle, J. (Box 8663)
- Wine of youth (Box 8664)
- Wingfield Manor (Box 8665)
- Winkler, Hubert (Box 8666)
- Winning his wings (Box 8667)
- Winslow, K. (Box 8668)
- Winter, D. (Box 8669)
- Winter R. (Box 8670)
- Winthrop (surname) (Box 8671)
- Wir sind die (Box 8672)
- Wirth, Max (Box 8673)
- Wirtschaftsstufen (Box 8674)
- Wisconsin. J. (Box 8675)
- Wisdom and the (Box 8676)
- Wise, Thomas James, 1859-1937. L. (Box 8677)
- Wisnu, S. (Box 8678)
- Wissenschaftlicher (Box 8679)
- Wit (titles, etc.) (Box 8680)
- Wither, George, 1588-1667. Fides-Anglicana (Box 8681)
- Witkiewicz, S.I. (Box 8682)
- Witte (Box 8683)
- Wittgenstein, Ludwig, 1889-1951 (continued) (Box 8684)
- Wittmann (Box 8685)
- Wladimirov, M. (Box 8686)
- Wo men ti k'ang (Box 8687)
- Wodehouse, Pelham Grenville. S. (Box 8688)
- Woerterbuch des (Box 8689)
- Woit (Box 8690)
- Wolcott family (Box 8691)
- Wolf, Hellmut (Box 8692)
- Wolfe (Box 8693)
- Wolfenbuetteler Symposion (Box 8694)
- Wolff, Johann (Box 8695)
- Wolfheim, J. (Box 8696)
- Wolkenstein, M. (Box 8697)
- Wolowski (Box 8698)
- Wolzogue, L. (Box 8699)
- Women (titles, etc.) (Box 8700)
- Women in exile (Box 8701)
- Women, work... (Box 8702)
- Womrath (Box 8703)
- Wonohito (Box 8704)
- Wood, F. (Box 8705)
- Wood, John S. (Box 8706)
- Wood, William, 1774-1857 (Box 8707)
- Woodbury (surname) (Box 8708)
- Woodhouse, J. (Box 8709)
- Woodruff (Box 8710)
- Woods, Robert S. (Box 8711)
- Woodward, H. (Box 8712)
- Woolbert (Box 8713)
- Woolley (Box 8714)
- Woolworth family (Box 8715)
- Worcester, Mass. Proprietors (Box 8716)
- Worden (Box 8717)
- Wordsworth, William, 1770-1850 (author) Prose... (Box 8718)
- Work f. (Box 8719)
- Working, R. (Box 8720)
- Working papers (Multinational Enterprises Programme) (Box 8721)
- Works of Virgil (Box 8722)
- World (Box 8723)
- World Bank. Loans at work (Box 8724)
- World city rankings (Box 8725)
- World d. (Box 8726)
- World Health Organization (Box 8727)
- World mender (Box 8728)
- World of the g. (Box 8729)
- World social economic conference (Box 8730)
- World's c. (Box 8731)
- Wormeley (Box 8732)
- Worsley (Box 8733)
- Wortman (Box 8734)
- Wozu (Box 8735)
- Wren, H. (Box 8736)
- Wright, Charles W. (Box 8737)
- Wright, G.H. (Box 8738)
- Wright, John H. (Box 8739)
- Wright, Quincy (Box 8740)
- Wright, T. (Box 8741)
- Wright (titles, etc.) (Box 8742)
- Writers' Program. Nebraska (Box 8743)
- Wrong (Box 8744)
- Wu, Chan-t'ai (Box 8745)
- Wu, Chien-ssu (Box 8746)
- Wu chung hsing (Box 8747)
- Wu Hsin-jung shu chien (Box 8748)
- Wu, Kuo (Box 8749)
- Wu, P'ing (Box 8750)
- Wu, Tai Te, 1935- (Box 8751)
- Wu, Wen-chih (Box 8752)
- Wuensch (Box 8753)
- Wuescher (Box 8754)
- Wunderer (Box 8755)
- Wurz (Box 8756)
- Wycherley (Box 8757)
- Wygal (Box 8758)
- Wymans, G. (Box 8759)
- Wyoming. Laws, statutes, etc. (Box 8760)
- Wythe (Box 8761)
- Xenakis (Box 8762)
- Xerox University. Microfilms (continued) (Box 8763)
- Y.M.C.A. Intern. convention (Box 8764)
- Yaborov (Box 8765)
- Yagui (Box 8766)
- Yakushi (Box 8767)
- Yale Club of W. (Box 8768)
- Yale Historical Publications. Studies (Box 8769)
- Yale New (Box 8770)
- Yale studies in English (Box 8771)
- Yale University (author) Obituary record (Box 8772)
- Yale University. Art Gallery (Box 8773)
- Yale University. Class of 1826 (Box 8774)
- Yale University. Class of 1950 (Box 8775)
- Yale University. Dwight (Box 8776)
- Yale University. L. (Box 8777)
- Yale University. Mabel Brady Garvin Coll. (Box 8778)
- Yale University. School of Medicine (Box 8779)
- Yale University. Sheffield scientific school. Class of 1900 (Box 8780)
- Yale University. Yale glee (Box 8781)
- Yale University-Curriculum (Box 8782)
- Yale University-Societies (Box 8783)
- Yalkut p. (Box 8784)
- Yamagata (Box 8785)
- Yamamoto (Box 8786)
- Yamanaka S. (Box 8787)
- Yamaya (Box 8788)
- Yanagita (Box 8789)
- Yang, Ch'eng-hou (Box 8790)
- Yang, F. (Box 8791)
- Yang, Keling (Box 8792)
- Yang, S. (Box 8793)
- Yang Tzu (Box 8794)
- Yankee songster (Box 8795)
- Yao, N. (Box 8796)
- Yardley (Box 8797)
- Yasqut (Box 8798)
- Yates, G. (Box 8799)
- Yazbek (Box 8800)
- Year Book of o. (Box 8801)
- Yeats, W.B. (William Butler), 1865-1939. O (Box 8802)
- Yeh, Ch'ien-yu (Box 8803)
- Yeh po (Box 8804)
- Yehudai (Box 8805)
- Yen (Box 8806)
- Yen, Hsi-chai (Box 8807)
- Yen, Su (Box 8808)
- Yepes (Box 8809)
- Yesterday in M. (Box 8810)
- Yidishe (Box 8811)
- Yin ling (Box 8812)
- Ying Han chi wei (Box 8813)
- Ying wu (Box 8814)
- Yo han (Box 8815)
- Yokaidan (Box 8816)
- Yolland (Box 8817)
- Yonge, Charlotte Mary, 1823-1901. R. (Box 8818)
- York v. (Box 8819)
- Yosano (Box 8820)
- Yoshida, Takashi (Box 8821)
- Yoshino (Box 8822)
- You can't h. (Box 8823)
- Young, Arthur B. (Box 8824)
- Young, Emily (Box 8825)
- Young, John Richardson (Box 8826)
- Young, Robert M. (Box 8827)
- Young folks (Box 8828)
- Younger (Box 8829)
- Youth (Box 8830)
- Yu, Ch'ang-min (Box 8831)
- Yu, Chun-cho (Box 8832)
- Yu Jen hua (Box 8833)
- Yu nien (Box 8834)
- Yu, Te-chun (Box 8835)
- Yu, Yin-shi (Box 8836)
- Yuan, Ming (Box 8837)
- Yuan Pi pei (Box 8838)
- Yueh chaun (Box 8839)
- Yugoslavia (author) (Box 8840)
- Yugoslavia (titles, etc.) (Box 8841)
- Yun (Box 8842)
- Yung (Box 8843)
- Yusei G. (Box 8844)
- Z (Box 8845)
- Z torby (Box 8846)
- Zablet (Box 8847)
- Zacher (Box 8848)
- Zafrani (Box 8849)
- Zaharia, N. (Box 8850)
- Zaide, S. (Box 8851)
- Zak (Box 8852)
- Zakonomemost (Box 8853)
- Zalutala (Box 8854)
- Zambrini (Box 8855)
- Zanabiq (Box 8856)
- Zanna, V. (Box 8857)
- Zapf (Box 8858)
- Zar lo (Box 8859)
- Zarnowska (Box 8860)
- Zasuto (Box 8861)
- Zavin (Box 8862)
- Zbaraski (Box 8863)
- Zea (Box 8864)
- Zeff (Box 8865)
- Zeinert, H. (Box 8866)
- Zeitschrift fuer (Box 8867)
- Zeitschrift fuer kristallographie (Box 8868)
- Zeki (Box 8869)
- Zeller, E. (Box 8870)
- Zemledelie na (Box 8871)
- Zenelis (Box 8872)
- Zenoni (Box 8873)
- Zer (Box 8874)
- Zeska (Box 8875)
- Zetterholm (Box 8876)
- Zhaloba (Box 8877)
- Zhilishcha R. (Box 8878)
- Zhonguo (Box 8879)
- Zibert (Box 8880)
- Ziegler, I. (Box 8881)
- Zierer (Box 8882)
- Zili (Box 8883)
- Zimmer (Box 8884)
- Zimmermann, H. (Box 8885)
- Zinck (Box 8886)
- Zinser (Box 8887)
- Zirkler (Box 8888)
- Zivotopis (Box 8889)
- Znachenie n. (Box 8890)
- Zoff (Box 8891)
- Zola, Emile, 1840-1902 (author) La joie de vivre (Box 8892)
- Zolotow (Box 8893)
- Zoologische Beitraege (Box 8894)
- Zorzi (Box 8895)
- Zschokke (Box 8896)
- Zuccala, M. (Box 8897)
- Zuercher E. (Box 8898)
- Zujovic (Box 8899)
- Zumbach (Box 8900)
- Zur B. (Box 8901)
- Zur Psychologie (Box 8902)
- Zusammenhang z. (Box 8903)
- Zwanzig, W. (Box 8904)
- Zweite W. (Box 8905)
- Zwingli t. (Box 8906)
- Zyla, W. (Box 8907)